

INFO

PROFESSION

Full Stack Developer

DATE OF BIRTH

29/Oct/1987

EMAIL

syyed.devcamp360@gmail.com

PHONE NUMBER

+92 332 479 1815

WEBSITE

https://ahsankazmi5.github.io/ahsandev/

ADDRESS

F-Block Satellite Town, Rawalpindi

EDUCATION

BACHELOR IN COMPUTER SCIENCE (2009 - 2013)

Riphah International University, islamabad

DIPLOMA IN ASSOCIATE

Swedish Institute of Technology

SYED AHSAN KAZMI

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER



PROFILE

I started my career in the agency world where I was given an opportunity to work on some amazing private brands. With this experience in my back pocket, I was able to land the role of a Full Stack Developer at Iplex.

In my free time I enjoy spending time with friends and family. Daily I go for at least a one hour walk while listening to music on Soundcloud, this is where I get most of my creative ideas. I love fast Bikes and have a Ride2, one day I hope to own a BMW K1200S, in the meantime I'll keep working hard towards my dream.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Feb 2021 - Present

Full Stack Senior Web Developer And Team Lead

BahriaTown Head Office, Rawalpindi

Sep 2019 - Feb 2021

Full Stack Developer

Lab270 KY, US

Aug 2016 - Sep 2019

Wordpress Developer

Iplex, BahriaTown

Nov 2014 - Feb 2015

Frontend Developer (Part Time Job)

Le Coder, Rawalpindi

Nov 2014 - Aug 2016

Junoir Web developer (Php, Forntend)

Iplex, Rawalpindi



RECENT PROJECTS

Autoplex Alberta https://www.autoplexalberta.ca/

Metal Buddies https://metalbuddies.com/

LIEBESTIPPS www.liebestipps.com

USA WILD SEA FOOD www.usawildseafoodapp.com

AVERAGE LOW www.averraglow.com

TRUCK TRANSPORT www.trucktransport.com

NTS MOVING www.ntsmoving.com

AUTO MOTIVE LEADS www.automotiveleads.com

PORSCHE www.porsche.dealerleads.com

COGNITOYS www.cognitoys.com

DCAS www.demo.dcas.biz

MY EXPERTISE

BACKEND/FRAMEWORKS

PHP

Wordpress

Shopify

Laravel

TOOLS/ARCHITECTURES

GitHub, Slack, Trello

Jira, Asana

WOOCOMMERCE STORE

WP Woocommece

Shopify Store

Templating online builders

FRONTEND

HTML5/CSS3/

Bootstrap

Javascript/jQuery

React.js

DATABASES

MySQI

Mongo.DB

DESIGN

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Experience (XD)

Adobe Illustrator



MY HOBBIES

- 1- Travel with Music
- 2- Sports (Cricket and Football)
- 3- Sketching
- 4- Streaming Videos (About Different Topics of History and Real Heroes)